Don't make this weird.
>> How can it be any weirder? This is goat
milking take one.
>> I've never milked a goat. I'm not going
to say. I'm a carpenter, a solar
professional, a content creator, a real
estate investor, not [music] a goat
milker. She doesn't have top teeth? She
got a trailer park mouth. Holy [__]
>> Hey, hey, hey, that goat started licking
me. She's not going to like this at all.
Goat milking take one.
Ooh. Yep. All right. Squeeze her out.
Got to get under there and wash all this
[music] stuff. Now what? But I don't
mind milking a goat. I ain't signed up
to wash his tit. Well, let me hold the
goat. Hold Nicole, you wash the stuff.
You really got to Oh god. Don't make
this weird.
>> How can it be any weirder? This is a
girl goat? It's like balls. They hanging
down, they floppy. Are there four
[music] or two? It's only two. I made it
through the whole chain gang without
doing this.
I'll steal. You hold her, I'm going to
go grab the bucket and
>> Oh, now I get to hold her. Show me what
you talking about.
>> Pinching? Nah, you milk her first.
>> Okay. So, pinch at the top and then
squeeze it. Pinch at the top and then
squeeze.
Whoa. Take a picture. You should lay
down
>> and let me squirt it right in your
mouth. Why don't you lay down and let me
squirt it right in your mouth?
>> me to squeeze the last bit out?
>> Yep. Don't let it kick the bucket.
That's one of the wildest things I've
ever done. How much milk have you drank
in your life and never once squeezed it
out of an animal? I'd be real thirsty if
I had to get up with milk like this.
I'll never take a glass of milk for
granted [music] again. She feel pretty
dry now. Taste the goat. That's not very
much milk. That was fun.
Our first goat milking [music] was a
success.